塞勒姆前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
私通者
Fornicator!
他在寻找
He searches.
那么女巫在哪
So where is the witch?
就在这里
Right here.
啊
Aaah!
如果不能阻止他
If he cannot be stopped,
那就变成一个全新的游戏了 不是吗
well, then it's an entirely new game, isn't it?
你父亲做的每一件事 都是为了你
Everything your father does, he does for you.
我不想再当你的顾客了
I no longer want to be your customer.
真爱不能买卖
True love cannot be bought or sold.
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
我们把梦变成现实吧
Let's just live.
你还爱着约翰 奥尔登
You still love John Alden.
那场盛大的仪式恰恰是在累觉不爱的心里腐败发酵的最好
The grand rite ferments best in a loveless heart.
翻译：爱吃  eva  bezero  呆毛
他听从于我的指令
He serves at my behest.
不会因为你跑出来的
He won't come out for you.
父亲
Father.
亲爱的因克里斯
My dear Increase.
校对：brian  慕斯
我们能够在镇上看到您多久呢
How long may we enjoy your presence in town?
一直到塞勒姆镇最后一个卖身魔鬼
Until every last Devil's whore of a witch
的女巫死光
in Salem is dead.
后期：hhjie
堕落
Depravity.
还能找到一个更恰当的词汇
Can there be a more apt word
来描述现阶段你们这个公平的城市吗
to describe the current state of your fair city?
酗酒 变态
Drink, perversity,
时间轴：阿黎
恶习 人们相互展示和感受到的
abominations of each and every variety
全都是这些
offered and received.
而且就在我们祀奉内心的魔鬼时
And even as we cater to our inner demons,
我们还让真正的恶魔肆无忌惮起来
we have allowed actual demons to flourish!
总监：柯小南
那些巫师们
Witches!
他不应该出现在这
He was not supposed to be here.
他应该在没有上帝保佑的航船上
Living vessels of godlessness.
那么为什么他在这
So why is he?
伊甸园的蛇
The serpent from eden...
他要来看看他的儿子取得了什么成就
He came to see what his son had accomplished.
你们都听说过
You have listened and...
那他为什么待着不走
And why is he staying?
因为他看到了他那儿子都干了些什么
He saw what his son had accomplished.
我们之中隐藏着巫师
There are witches hidden amongst us,
而在塞勒姆的你们
and you people of Salem,
被饮酒和淫乱引诱
seduced by drink and by flesh,
一步步沉迷不醒
are happily blinded to it.
我在此
Standing before you,
在青天白日之下
with the certainty of the rising sun,
向你们保证 这一切将会改变
I assure you this will change.
西布利夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
牧师 您的话语非常鼓舞人心
Reverend, your words are inspiration.
您回来是英格兰的损失 是我们的好运
England's loss is our gain.
我相信你丈夫的情况一定是越来越好了
I trust your husband's condition is improving.
不幸的是并没有
Sadly, no.
那就帮我告诉乔治
Well, please tell George
我不久就会再去看他
I shall visit him again at once.
也许我的探望能够让他感觉好一点
Perhaps my presence may be of some comfort to him.
哦 那是肯定的
Oh, how could it not?
妙不可言啊
I have no words.
就像是对于看到了上帝面容的人来说
Like a man who's seen the face of God.
只有因敬畏而无声才是最好的表达方式
Only an awed silence is the appropriate response.
你父亲
Your father.
你这样一说 真是毁情绪啊
And like that, the mood is ruined.
不 你 你父亲
No, your... your father.
他正 他在人群中
He's... he's in the common.
前呼后拥 当然了 把他说的每一个字都奉若真理
With a crowd, no doubt, hanging on his every word.
他是 被前呼后拥 但是他没说话
With a crowd, yes, but he's not speaking.
那你还是让他跟别人困扰去吧
Well, then you must have him confused with someone else.
他正朝这边过来
He's walking this way.
你说的朝这边 意思是
And by "This way," You mean...
不能让他看到我在这
He cannot find me here.
而要开始清洗我们的塞勒姆镇
And where better to begin our cleansing of Salem
哪能比这肮脏至极的淫窟更合适呢
than in its most vile den?
后边楼梯
The back stairs.
不 不 不 不对 你 那你得穿过平台
No, no, no, no, y-you'll cross the landing.
格洛丽安娜 我父亲不会理解我的
Gloriana, my father does not understand me.
他从来都不
He never has.
-如果让他发现我 -快藏在床底下
- If he discovers me... - Gloriana: Under the bed now.
-什么 快藏在床底下
What?! - Gloriana: Under the bed now!
我的圣经呢
Where's my Bible?
我 我 我没看见
I-I-I don't see it!
哦
Oh.
麦哲牧师
Reverend Mather.
你认识我
You know me?
整个省里面谁不认识您呢
Is there anyone in the province who doesn't?
你一个人吗
You are alone?
不是
No.
我与我的上帝同在
I'm here with my lord.
还有他的话
His words, anyway.
在最危险的时候 那些话给了我极大的安慰
They offer great comfort in these perilous times...
即使是对像我这样的女人来讲
Even for a woman like me.
你们感觉不到吗
Do you not sense it?
罪孽和巫术混杂在一起
The commingling of sin and sorcery?
深呼吸
Take a breath.
你甚至可以尝到它
You can almost taste it...
撒旦的毒酒
Satan's toxic nectar,
为了转移你们的注意 平息你们的怒火
designed to divert and disarm.
啊
Ah.
这温柔乡的女主人
The proprietress of this charming establishment.
今天要什么样的啊 牧师
What'll it be today, Reverend?
纤瘦柔软的
Thin and pliant,
还是丰满调皮的
or thick and playful?
跟长辈说话要小心 女士
Mind your betters, madam.
我做的是清白生意 你什么都抓不到
I run an honest house. You'll find nothing here.
我就是以我之名立誓 要在你这什么都抓不到的地方
I have made my name finding things
抓到点东西
where there is nothing to be found.
鸢尾根
Orris root?
陌生人每天进进出出
Strangers tramp in and out of here every day.
我不能确定他们都有什么目的
I do not know what substances they carry.
嗯
Hmm.
铸造石
Casting stones.
塞勒姆的治安官啊
Selectmen of Salem...
我们发现了一个女巫
We've uncovered a witch.
我们之中有人
One of ours.
在我们最惶恐的时候弃船了
Exactly what we feared the minute he stepped off that ship.
现在 你们知道这意味着什么了
Now, well, you know what this means.
就算我没跟你一起恐慌
Just because I don't share your panic
也不代表我没发现问题所在
doesn't mean I don't grasp the stakes.
他会向她逼问我们的名字
He will press her for names,
你觉得她最先会供出谁呢
and whose will be she tempted to provide?
她太大意了
She was careless,
竟然把能泄露身份的东西留在身边
leaving objects of her craft so close at hand.
就因为她的失误 我们都将会被烧死
And for that carelessness, we may all burn,
更别提还想举行什么盛大的仪式了
to say nothing of what will become of our grand rite.
你在这歇斯底里也无济于事
Your hysteria offers no solutions.
马布只是需要一个小小的提醒 什么才是我们想要她做的
Mab simply needs to be reminded what is expected of her.
她的缄默
Her silence.
你是对的
You're right.
我马上就去看她
I shall pay her a visit at once.
你在担心
You're worried.
他让人生畏 老麦哲
He is formidable, the senior Mather,
一边恐吓一边狩猎
part bully, part bloodhound.
马布自始至终都忠于我们巫群
Mab has been loyal to the hive throughout.
让我担心的不是马布
It is not Mab that worries me.
因克里斯说要再来拜访
Increase promises to pay another visit.
你觉得还需要多久他才发现
How long before he realizes
乔治不是生病了而是被下蛊
that George is not sick, but spelled?
又是被谁下的毒手 是我
And at whose hands? Mine.
那就阻止他
Then prevent this.
对
Yes.
因克里斯是想他方便的时候才来
Increase may visit at his pleasure,
而什么原因能让挚爱的妻子在卧病在床的丈夫最需要照看的时候
for what loving wife would leave her ailing husband at home
将其独自留在家中呢
when his condition demands attention at once?
今天这么早就喝酒了
You're drinking early today.
如果你了解我父亲
If you knew my father,
如果你了解我的父亲
你就会为我能等如此之久而称赞我了
you'd commend me for waiting this long.
你知道吗 你把你父亲说得像是
You know, the way you speak of him, you make him sound...
没有人性
Inhuman?
-对 -好样的
-Yes. -Good.
看来我对他的描述丝毫不差
Then I have painted an accurate picture.
你不信吗 你自己瞧瞧
Don't believe me? See for yourself.
柯顿 我一整个早上都在找你
Cotton, I've been in search of you all morning.
我早该料到
I supposed I should have realized
你泡在酒坛子里了
you would be somewhere where whiskey is served.
老爸 这是约翰
Father, this is John...
约翰 奥尔登
John Alden.
你父亲和我是大学同学
Your father and I were classmates at university.
我知道
Yes, I know.
很荣幸见到你 上尉
An honor, Captain.
真的 我对你无比尊敬
Truly, I can have no greater respect
因为你在战场上舍生忘死
than for a man who has risked his life in battle.
可悲了 现在不是所有的年轻人都有你这样的勇气
Sadly, not all young men possess the same mettle.
什么风把你吹来了 父亲
What brings you, father?
我十分惊奇地发现
Well, I am shocked to discover
塞勒姆竟然自甘堕落伤风败俗到这种程度
the extent of the depravity and immorality in Salem.
人们需要有人来提醒他们犯下罪孽后的代价
The people need a reminder of the wages of their sin.
不是不报 时候未到
And so they will get one.
-哼 -在周日的布道上
-Mm-hmm. -In Sunday's sermon.
不 不
No. No.
他们需要听到你的声音 就是此刻
They need to hear your voice now.
给平民的公众朗诵
A public recitation on the commons,
用蒙上罪孽的脸来阐述
illustrated by the face of sin.
蒙上罪孽的脸
The face of sin?
那是谁
And who is that?
柯顿
And Cotton?
你的圣经
Your Bible.
波士顿的医院在等他
The hospital in Boston awaits him.
它是我寻到治愈方法的唯一希望了
It is my only hope to find a cure
他的情况日趋严重
for his worsening condition.
以撒 你对我丈夫的感觉
And, Isaac, your feelings towards my husband
针对他曾经做过的事
for what he once did...
是可以理解的
They're understandable,
但是你在他最需要的时候帮助他
but to help him in his hour of need
为我展示了你的真正度量
shows me the true measure of you...
我为此对你永怀感激
For which I am forever grateful.
我们在黎明时会到波士顿
We will be in Boston by daybreak.
我能见一下被告吗
A moment with the accused?
好的 地方官
Yes, magistrate.
你是来杀我的
You've come here to kill me.
这是我的分内之事
It would be within my right to do so.
家有家法 国有国规
The code of the hive is clear.
但是 不 我们同意饶恕你
But, no, we have agreed to spare you.
我决不允许发生第二次
I would allow nothing else.
但是 在目前这个问题上
Still... to the issue at hand.
他会审问你
He will interrogate you.
我会守口如瓶
And I will give him nothing.
到死我都不会出卖女巫的事业
I will swallow the blackened pill before I betray the cause.
这就是你的目的 是的
That will be your intent, yes,
直到他拷问你
until he tortures you
然后 听到你痛苦的嘶喊
and then, hearing your cries of pain,
他会更加残忍地拷问你
tortures you some more,
此时你就会哀求他
at which point you will beg for him
让你说出一个名字
to allow you to offer a name,
甚至只是为了暂时逃离肉体的痛苦
even if only to release yourself from the agony.
当这一切发生的时候
When that happens...
它会发生的
And it will happen...
我只能分散你的注意力
I have just the distraction for you to provide.
父亲 你晚上去哪里了
Where do you go at night, father?
安妮 还没睡呢
Anne. Awake at this hour?
母亲说我不应该问这种问题
Mother says I shouldn't ask such questions,
我仅仅需要
that I should simply be grateful
对你为了我们所做出的牺牲表示感激
for the sacrifices you make on our behalf.
胡说 随便问
Nonsense. Ask whatever you like.
今晚我在专心处理这个镇上的事务
Tonight I was preoccupied with business of the town.
你相信她是个女巫吗
And do you believe she is a witch?
谁
Who?
你在监狱里找到的那个女人
The woman you sought out at the jail.
你跟踪我
You followed me?
我只是想知道那些所谓的牺牲究竟是什么
I simply wanted to know what those sacrifices were
为什么它们总是见不得阳光
and why they seem to be so often made in secret.
起先你私窥我的房间
First you snoop about in my room,
翻看我的东西 而现在
unearthing my belongings, and now...
不
No.
不 什么意思
No? What?
不 我不相信她是女巫
No, I do not believe she is a witch.
她只是个可爱又可怜的女人
She is but a sad, lonely woman.
我很高兴听到
I am glad to hear
塞勒姆的人还有些常识
there is some common sense left in Salem.
晚安 父亲
Good night, father.
晚安 亲爱的
Good night, dear.
求你 我是无辜的
Please! I am innocent!
你为你使用巫术的罪孽进行辩护
You have pled guilty to the practice of witchcraft.
但是这种辩护并不足以使你脱罪
But such a plea is not sufficient to spare your life.
我需要的是名单
I want names of others.
我不知道
I know of no others.
再来
Again.
不 我发誓我是无辜的
No! I swear I'm innocent!
他疯了
He's insane.
在如此美好的一天
On a good day.
啊
Aah!
只要说出一个你的同伙
Only the name of a fellow witch
你就会被赦免
will spare your life.
没有同伙
I know of no others.
我再问一遍 先警告你
I will ask again, but first a caution.
下一次 海水可不仅仅只填满你的嘴巴
The next time, the saltwater that filled your mouth only
你的喉咙 你的肺都会充斥了海水
will travel down your throat into your lungs.
然后你挣扎着要辨别的滋味
And then the taste you struggle to discern
不是海水味 不是空气 而是死亡
will not be of water, nor of air, but of death.
名字
A name.
等一下
Wait!
我只等你说出一个同伙的名字
And I wait only for the name of a fellow witch.
我会告诉你的
And I will give it to you.
是她 格洛丽安娜
Her! Gloriana!
不可能
No.
不可能 不可能
No. No. No!
这肯定是弄错了 不可能的 父亲 这肯定弄错了
This is a mistake. No, father, this is a mistake.
昂布里小姐不是女巫
Miss embry is no witch.
你来这儿只是旁观 不应插手此事
You are here to observe, not to interfere.
听我说 父亲
Listen to me, father.
这正是我设法要告诉你的
This is what I have tried to tell you,
现在我目睹了它是对的 就是我们都错了
and now I see it to be true... That we have been wrong.
柯顿
Cotton.
我们一腔热血
That in our zeal
想要驱逐撒旦
to rid Satan from our midst,
却变成了屠戮无辜
we are instead killing innocents.
不要对我说教
Do not presume to instruct me.
我们是在助纣为虐啊
We are doing the Devil's work for him!
所以我倾其一生的事业是个错误
And my life's work is a mistake?
尊敬地说 是的
Respectfully... yes.
靠边站
Stand aside.
求你 父亲 求求你 放了她吧
Please, father, I beg you... spare her.
滚开
Get out of my way.
请听我说
Listen to me!
我听着
I have.
我不会再让你扮演傻瓜
And I will no longer let you act the fool.
你确定我就是那个傻瓜吗
You are sure it is I who acts the fool?
柯顿
Cotton.
把她关进笼子
Take her to the cage.
柯顿 柯顿
Cotton. Cotton!
不要
No.
柯顿 柯顿
Cotton! Cotton!
上帝啊 怎么了 西布利先生
Oh, Lord. What is it, Mr. Sibley?
努力呼吸一下 西布利先生 就是这样
Try to breathe, Mr. Sibley. That's it.
慢慢呼吸 西布利先生
Slow breath, Mr. Sibley.
就是这样
That's right.
就是这样 很好很简单
That's it, nice and easy.
不
No!
父亲
Father!
父亲 你没有任何证据
Father, you have no evidence.
胡说 我有那个被公认为的女巫的供词
Nonsense. I have the word of an admitted witch.
就是那个耍魔鬼巫术的女人
A woman who practices the Devil's craft?
你竟然相信她去指认其他人
You trust her to finger others?
告诉我
Tell me...
是不是所有的控告都让你肾上腺素飙升
Do all accusations stir such passions in you?
或者那个妓女的案子有什么特别之处吗
Or is there something unique about the whore's case?
我知道这些人 我生活在他们中间
I know these people. I have lived among them.
西布里小姐不是撒旦的工具
Miss embry is no tool of Satan.
那如果她做魔鬼烙印的测试呢
And if she were to be examined for the Devil's marks?
测试
An examination?
我有这个自信
I'm confident...
不 我确信 你们什么都找不到
No, I am certain... That you would find nothing.
事实上 是的 我支持你去做这件事
In fact, yes, I would encourage you to settle the issue
即刻执行测试
and conduct the exam at once.
我 不
Me? No.
不是 我把这事儿交给你去办
No, I will leave that to you.
你去测试被告
You will examine the accused.
上尉
Captain.
不
No.
约翰
John!
这不是我要的反应
That wasn't the reaction I was expecting.
也不是我要的问候
Nor the greeting I was.
那天晚上
The other night...
我们说过的 做过的
What we said... what we did.
什么 你后悔了
What, do you regret it?
不
No.
我唯一的遗憾就是我们再也不能那样了
My only regret is that it can never happen again.
我已经结婚了 约翰
I'm a married woman, John.
和一个疾病缠身的男人
With a very sick husband.
西布利先生再也不能顺我心的死去了
Mr. Sibley would never do me the favor of dying.
我们都知道这点
We both know that.
他被送去医院了
He was taken to hospital.
他肯定会回来的
From where he will surely return...
一如既往的活着 享受婚姻
As alive and married as ever.
就是这个原因
Is that the reason?
西布利夫人
Sibley?
没有其他了
Nothing else?
不是因为恐惧吗
Not a fear?
或者某个你觉得我接受不了的秘密
Or a secret that you think I couldn't accept?
因为塞勒姆从来没有人
Because there is no one in Salem
能够卸下沉重的过往
unburdened by their past...
我也不能
Not even me.
对不起 西布利
I'm sorry, John.
我希望你能理解
I hope you can understand.
父亲 求求你
Father, please.
开始
Proceed.
没有印记
No marks.
把她翻过来
Turn her.
什么都没有
Nothing.
把她衣服撩起来
Raise her smock.
依然什么都没有
Still nothing.
上半身
The upper torso.
父亲
Father...
上半身
The upper torso.
等一下
Wait.
所以你看 就像我保证的
So, you see, as I assured you,
他身上没有恶魔使者的标志
she bears no signs of a Devil's agent,
没有疤痕 没有女巫乳头
no blemishes, no witches' teats.
这些我都会在她的审判上提及
All of which I will be sure to mention at her trial.
她还要审判
Her trial?
但我已经向你证明了她身上没有标记
But I have proven to you she is without marks.
你忘了嘛 我们不是法官
Have you forgotten? We are not judges.
我们只是寻找真相
We are simply seekers of the truth.
审判权在行政委员手上
The power of verdict rests with the selectmen.
这里是塞勒姆 你知道他们会怎样投票
This is Salem. You know how they will vote.
那你正好把你的愤怒
Well, then you save
你的放肆无礼向他们发泄吧
your rage and your impudence for them.
你看到了吧 今天又有个女人被指控为女巫
Another woman was accused today... as you saw.
这场女巫恐慌简直要把人逼疯了
It's madness, this witch panic.
是的 真令人惋惜
Yes, it is regrettable.
惋惜
Regrettable?
你想要我干什么
What would you have me do?
你可以站出来反驳他们
You could speak out, rail against it.
你有一堆选择 可你却什么都不做
You have any number of options beyond nothing.
我孤掌难鸣啊 也许你对我期望值太高了
I am one man. Perhaps you expect too much of me.
也许你为这做的太少了
Perhaps you are content with too little.
注意你的言辞 孩子
Hold your tongue, child.
我就是不理解
I just don't understand
为什么他如此乐意看到人们被绞死
why he's so content to see people hang...
好像他内心对此暗暗欢喜似的
Almost as if he secretly likes it.
我不喜欢你含沙射影
I don't appreciate the insinuation.
我哪里含沙射影了
What insinuation is that?
你是想说我是那种
That I was somehow in league
内心尖刻的清教徒
with the murdering puritans.
噢 不 我根本不是这个意思
Oh, no, that was not my insinuation at all.
事实上 恰恰相反
In fact, it was quite the opposite.
那你是什么意思
And what might that be?
是这样 我 我突然感觉很累
You know, I'm... I'm suddenly very tired.
你到底在指责我什么
What are you accusing me of?
我想我该去躺一会儿
I think I should lie down.
安妮 你解释清楚前哪都不准去
Anne, do not walk away until you have explained yourself.
安妮
Anne!
我能问你个问题嘛
May I ask you a question?
他为什么讨厌你
Why does he hate you?
原因只有两个
Two reasons only...
一是我的所作所为
For what I am...
二是我的无所作为
And what I am not.
那么你已经向他表明了 你站在那姑娘那边了
And you've appealed to him on the girl's behalf?
再说一遍 他根本不鸟我
Repeatedly. He does not regard me.
说实话 他不鸟任何人
Truth told, he does not regard anyone except...
除了你 约翰
For you, John.
柯顿 这不可能
Cotton, no.
他希望我成为像你一样的人
You are everything he ever wished me to be.
你是战争英雄
You are a hero in war.
坚毅刚强
You are a man without weakness or frailty.
柯顿 无意冒犯
Cotton, I'm sorry.
去乞求一个混蛋清教徒正确行事
Begging another puritan asshole to do the right thing?
成功过么
Since when has it worked?
-现在又怎么会成功 -你说得没错
- And why would it work now? - You're right.
任何人都不该被迫在我父亲面前低声下气 卑躬屈膝
No man should be forced to humble himself before my father.
我到塞勒姆已经好几个月了
I have been in Salem for months.
有很多朋友也有不少敌人
I have made allies and enemies in scores.
但我最亲近的朋友
But the closest thing that I have come to a friend...
是你
Is you.
所以我希望你
So I ask you...
我乞求你
I beg you...
去找我父亲说情
To appeal to my father,
如果你稍微有一点看得起我
if there is some small part of you
也能称我一声朋友的话
that can call me a friend, too.
西布利先生
Mr. Sibley?
Mr. Sibley?!
西布利先生
Mr. Sibley.
救命 以撒
Help me, Isaac.
你能说话了
You can speak.
神奇的上帝重赋我言语之能
The Lord's miraculous workings.
你在流血
You're leaking blood.
所以救救我
Which is why I need your help.
快去塞勒姆
Go to Salem.
给我带医生和药品来
Return with supplies and one to administer them.
要我帮你
Help you?
是的
Yes.
你还记得你烙印我的那一天嘛
Do you remember the day you marked me?
你在我身上烙下私通者的印记的那天
The day you seared my flesh with the sign of the fornicator?
你还记得吗
You remember that?
我想这之后你没有一刻
And I would imagine that not a moment has since passed
不希望我死
that you didn't wish me dead.
现在机会来了 你甚至不用动一根手指头
And now your chance, without even raising a hand.
只要你走开 我就必死无疑
Walk away, and I will surely die here.
我为什么不呢
Why shouldn't I?
因为在你期待复仇的同时
Because while you desired revenge
我真心为这样对你而感到后悔
I bore regret for what I did.
说得好听
Words.
那你帮帮我 我会给予你更多
Then help me, and I will shower you
不光是美言 更有黄金
not with words, but gold,
比你期望的还要多的黄金
more than you've ever hoped to possess.
黄金
Gold?
只要把药和 和西布利夫人带来就行了么
To return with... with medicines and Mrs. Sibley?
不
No.
不是她
Not her.
是因克瑞斯
Increase.
因克瑞斯
Increase?
别跟我妻子说
Tell my wife nothing.
快去把因克瑞斯 马瑟带来
Bring me Increase Mather at once.
快去 小子
Go now, boy!
快
Run!
请进
Yes?
牧师
Reverend.
不行
The answer is no.
我还什么都没说
I didn't ask a question.
你是来为那个妓女求情的对吧
You're here to beg for the whore's life, are you not?
我那糊涂儿子叫你来的对吧
Dispatched by my besotted son, no doubt.
是的
Yes.
那我就开门见山的说了 奥尔登队长
Well, let me save you the trouble, Captain Alden.
她是一定会接受审判的
The decision has been made to take her to trial.
但请放心 我一定会告诉柯顿
But rest assured I will be sure to tell Cotton
你真心诚意的为她求过情了
that your pleas were most heartfelt.
先生 格罗丽安娜不是女巫
Sir... Gloriana is no witch.
没错 她不是
No.
但我想你也知道 她迷惑了我儿子
But I think you will agree she has bewitched my son.
你知道 我父亲是十分敬重你的 牧师
You know, my father held you in high regard, Reverend.
奥尔登先生 是个好人
Alden sr. Was a good man.
他的世界观与众不同
He viewed the world with uncommon reason.
没错 可在育儿方面却也与他人无异
Yeah, well, except when it came to his own son.
他希望我研习经文
He wanted me to study scripture,
但我却选择去森林探险
and I chose to explore the woods.
他希望我去读大学
He wanted me to attend university,
而我却志愿去参军
and I volunteered for war.
他到死都认定我一生的选择都是错的
He went to his grave thinking my life's choices mistakes.
即便如此他也同意你这么做
And yet he allowed you to make them.
是的 因为他懂得就事论事
Well, that's because he knew the difference.
就事论事
Between?
可以不爱他儿子的选择
Between loving his son's choices
但还是爱他的儿子
and loving his son.
奥尔登队长
Captain Alden.
以撒 怎么了
Isaac, what is it?
借一步说话
Not here.
乔治西布利能说话了
George Sibley can speak?
就像我们一样口齿清晰
As clearly as you or I.
他受伤了 却不要见他的妻子
And wounded, he doesn't request his wife,
-而是要见 -因克瑞斯 马瑟
- but asks for... -Increase Mather.
他就像贼一样不可信
I trust him no more than a thief.
但真要违抗那样位高权重的人吗
But to disobey a man of his standing?
你什么都别做
Then do nothing.
队长
Captain?
你征求我的意见所以我发表观点
You sought my advice, so I offer it.
任他自生自灭
Do nothing.
但是 再把他丢在
But to leave him any longer
荒郊野外 他还在流血
than I have in the woods, bleeding...
他会死的
He will die.
是的
Yes.
他罪有应得不是吗
Does he deserve anything less?
他在你的身体上烙下了印记
The man who marked your flesh...
把我派上了战场
Drove me to war...
还像暴君一般统治着塞勒姆
And has ruled over Salem like a power-mad king?
现在 他凭什么乞求怜悯
And now, what, he begs for compassion?
还有合作
Cooperation?
怎么
What?
我知道你爱她 队长
I know you love her, Captain.
但不管他的死活就是谋杀
But to leave him to die is murder.
什么都 别干
Do... nothing.
不 你要带我去哪
No. Where are you taking me?
告诉我 你要带我去哪
Tell me! Where are you taking me?!
塞勒姆善良的人们
Good people of Salem,
我已经注意到了
it has come to my attention
今天这场指控
that the accusation leveled today
是女巫们的一个把戏
was a trick of the witches...
一个欺骗和混淆视听的邪恶把戏
An infernal ploy to delude and distract from the truly guilty.
这个女人不是女巫
This woman is no sorceress.
因此 她不会被审判
And therefore she will not go to trial.
但这个女人自甘堕落
But what her advocates fail to grasp
不是女巫并不能说明她无罪
is that absence of guilt does not mean innocence...
所以这个妓女绝不是无辜的
For this whore is no innocent... Far from it.
她有罪，肉体之罪
She is guilty of sin, sins of the flesh,
她冒犯上帝 人神共愤
sins against God, sins both mortal and eternal,
因此 她不能再涉足塞勒姆半步
and as such, she warrants no place in Salem.
不
No.
所以 我宣判
And so, by my decree,
她现被驱逐出此地
she is hereby banished from our midst,
即刻生效 不容异议
her expulsion immediate and beyond dispute.
现在你 看着我
And should she... Look at me...
永远 不论何种缘由
Ever return at any time,
不得再回到塞勒姆
for any reason,
你如果再次出现在这里
you will find yourself once again beside me on the common,
你肮脏的躯体
your lifeless body dangling
将依旧会被侩子手终结
from the wrong end of the hangman's noose.
带她走吧
Take her.
柯顿
Cotton!
格洛丽安娜 -柯顿 柯顿
Gloriana! - Cotton! Cotton!
柯顿 柯顿
Cotton! Cotton!
格洛丽安娜 -后退 后退
Gloriana! -Stand back. Stay back.
不 格洛丽安娜
No! Gloriana!
对不起
I'm sorry.
带她走 直到路的尽头
Take her as far as your steeds will travel.
并宣告天下
And let it be known
无论是罪恶还是罪人
neither sin nor sinner
在塞勒姆都无立足之地
have any place in Salem.
乔治
George.
我不知道是谁 是怎样做到的
I don't know how or by whom,
但他已经变了
but the familiar has been excised from him.
他现在可能正在任何地方告诉任何人
He could be anywhere right now, talking to anyone.
我们做的一切
All that we've worked for,
我所有的牺牲 瞬间消失殆尽
all that I've sacrificed, incinerated in an instant.
冷静下来帮帮我
Calm yourself and help me.
世界之大 皆在变幻
Mutare, et notum sumbotis.
表象之躯 皆为指引
Forma enim esse ostendit.
躯体为本 魂魄为体
Corpus, anima, mens.
指引我找到那个人
Lead me to the one I seek.
它会带领我找到他
The creature will lead me to him.
幸运的话 我会尽快找到他
With luck, I will find him quickly.
没有它 我们都可能会被烧死
And without it, we shall all burn.
你采用了我的方法啊
You take issue with my methods.
我懂
I understand.
你要知道 我做的每一件事
What you need to understand is that everything I have done
都是为了让你能担得起马瑟这个名字
has been to make you worthy of the Mather name.
我爱她
I loved her.
不要那么说
Do not say that.
我不说话 不代表不爱她
My silence does not make it untrue.
若有一天
One day,
当你统治这片伟大的土地时
when you are governor of this great land,
权利与道德并拥
a man of power and a model of virtue,
受到大家敬重
respected and feared in equal measure,
你会想到今天
you will trace it back to this day...
我将你前进之路的诱惑一一铲除
The day I removed temptation from your path.
-服务员 -有什么需要吗
-You there. - Yes?
给我一份红茶 要浓的
Bring me some black tea, very strong, if you please.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你不是昨天那个
Are you not the young man
把西布利带到波士顿的人吗
who transported Mr. Sibley to Boston yesterday?
是的 我叫以撒
Isaac, sir.
-以撒 -嗯
-Isaac. -Mm.
已经去过波士顿 都回来了
Boston and back?
还真快啊
Record time.
你真的是个不错的骑士
You must be quite the horseman, Isaac.
不 我可不敢妄称
No, I-I wouldn't say that.
啊 告诉我
Well, tell me.
医生对病人的情况
Did the physician offer any insight
有没有提出什么见解
into the patient's condition?
医生
Physician?
诊断 或者是 预测
A diagnosis? Or a prognosis?
嗯
Um...
不 我不能
No, I can't...
你确实把西布利
Well, you did take Mr. Sibley
送到了医院吧 难道不是吗
to the hospital, did you not?
你支支吾吾什么
What is it you are not saying?
以撒 看着我
Isaac... look at me.
告诉我你们此次的真实经过
Tell me the truth about your journey.
患者现在在大陆正南方向
The injured is due South, inland,
通往波士顿的一条树林路中
on the wooded path to Boston.
驾
Hyah!
让开
Clear the way.
谁在那 快现身
Who's there? Show yourself.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫柏翠
The name is Petrus.
不到一小时之前 我看到你睡着了
Not an hour ago, I spied you sleeping,
看到你受伤了 我就回去给你拿了一些药
and, seeing your grave wound, I have returned with medicinals.
停 不要再靠近我了
Stop. Not one step closer.
但是 先生 你已经感染了
But, sir, an infection has already taken root.
不要担心 救助人员马上到
Do not worry yourself. Aid is on the way.
但是你不疼吗
But you are in pain, are you not?
我带了这个药可以减轻你的疼痛感
I have concocted a simple physic to ease your suffering.
谁都不该像你一样遭受这些
No creature, man or animal, should suffer as you do, sir.
给
Please.
你给我的是什么
What have you given me?
对不起 先生
I am truly sorry, sir.
她创造了我
She made me.
我们要把他带到你的小屋去
We will take him to your shack
直到危险解除
until the threat has passed.
西布利 你就真的认为
Did you really think it would be so easy
能如此简单的逃过我们
to escape us, Mr. Sibley?
在这 向前走
There, up ahead!
乔治 乔治
George? George?
你是他的仆人
You're the servant?
是的 是西布利夫人派来
Yes, sir, sent by Mrs. Sibley
找回她生病的丈夫的
to retrieve her ailing husband.
这比我想象的还要糟糕
This is worse than I had feared.
所以我才要他立即去医院治疗
Which is why he needs to be taken to hospital at once.
不
No.
困扰我的不是他的病
It is not the injury that troubles me,
而是他如何得病的
but how he came by it.
他试图摆脱女巫对他的控制
He sought to free himself from the witches' grip.
我不懂
I do not understand.
他没生病
The man is not ill.
他被下咒了
He has been spelled.
你对这知道多少
Might you know something about that?
黑尔小姐
Miss Hale.
你记不记得那天下午在墓园
Do you remember that afternoon in the graveyard,
你向我暗示我的父亲并不是我们所想的那样
when you implied my father is not who he seems?
记得
Yes.
请我进来 我告诉你为什么我也这么觉得
Invite me inside, and I'll tell you why I agree.
告诉我 西布利先生在哪
Tell me... where is Mr. Sibley?
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
那不是我的问题
That was not my question.
你要么知道他在哪 要么就不知道
Either you know where he is, or you don't.
我确实知道他在哪
I do know where he is,
而那就是问题
and that is the problem.
牧师认为他被下咒了
The Reverend has deemed him a victim of witchcraft
决定带着乔治去他那边休养
and has decided that George is to rest under his care.
我们应该快一点了
Quickly now. Make haste.
天啊
My God.
柏翠的巫术只能维持一天
Petrus' physic will last but a day.
在那
There. There.
然后 西布利会醒来 神志清楚
And then Mr. Sibley will awake, lucid and eager.
会亟不可待地告诉因科瑞斯一切
To tell Increase everything.